PRIVACY STATEMENT
=================

Your privacy is important to LinangData. This privacy statement provides information about the Personal Information that LinangData collects, and the ways in which LinangData uses that Personal Information.

Personal Information collection
-------------------------------

LinangData may collect and use Personal Information about your use of this website, namely information about browsing and linking ("Personal Information");

The Tools available on LinangData, namely, formatters, validators, encoders & decoders, code beautifiers, generators, converters, string utilities, and other web resources available on linangdata.com (the "Tools") are primarily client-side tools and do not store data on a server.

Where a tool uses a third-party API, LinangData does not make any representation or guarantee how this data is used by the third-party API. For example, the "Grammar & Style" tool, is processed by a third-party API provided by https://languagetool.org.

Using Personal Information
--------------------------

LinangData may use your Personal Information to administer this website; enable your access to and use of the website services; and improve the services it offers and monitor the traffic and Tools usage;

We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as cookies, browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers, Google Analytics, Microsoft Clarity, and Facebook Social ("Third Party Add-Ons")). LinangData does not track Sensitive Information or single users. We at LinangData use Google Analytics to collect data. We need this data to understand how you use our website so we can improve its design and functionality. We also need the data to get the most out of our marketing campaigns.

We may collect information about your computer, including IP addresses, OS and browser type for system administration and to report general information to our advertisers. This data is statistical about browsing actions and patterns and does not identify any individual user.

We may obtain information about general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. Cookies help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They allow us to estimate audience size and usage, remember your preferences and recently used features when you return to our site, and allow us to customize our site according to your individual interests.

You can refuse to accept cookies by adjusting your browser to refuse setting of cookies. If you do this you may be unable to access certain parts of our site.

No data or file uploaded to LinangData's servers is read, analysed or processed.

Google Analytics
----------------

The Website uses a tool called “**Google Analytics**” to collect information about use of the Website. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this Website, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other websites they used prior to coming to this Website. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to maintain and improve the Website and our products. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with Personal Information we collect. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this Website is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Service, available at [https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/analytics/terms/us/](https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/analytics/terms/us/), and the Google Privacy Policy, available at [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). You may learn more about how Google collects and processes data specifically in connection with Google Analytics at [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You may prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics by downloading and installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on, available at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

Google Signals
--------------

.

The Website uses a tool called “**Google Signals**” to collect information about use of the Website. When we activate Google Signals, some existing Google Analytics features are updated to also include aggregated data from Google users who have turned on “Ads Personalization” (Ads Personalization available at [https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662856/](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662856/)). Audiences that we create in Google Analytics and publish to Google Ads and other Google Marketing Platform advertising products can serve ads in cross device-eligible remarketing campaigns to Google users who have turned on Ads Personalization. Google Analytics collects additional information about users who have turned on Ads Personalization, base across device types and on aggregated data from users who have turned on Ads Personalization. The data is user based rather than session based. The Cross Device reports include only aggregated data. No data for individual users is ever exposed. Youcan modify your interests, choose whether your Personal Data is used to make ads more relevant to you, and turn on or off certain advertising services in the Ads Personalization link above.

Sensitive Information
---------------------

Before submitting documents containing Sensitive Information such as information pertaining to someone's health, finances, proprietary data, security data, biometric data, or any information otherwise considered confidential ("Sensitive Information") users should obtain prior consent from their respective security officer, compliance officer or legal department to do so.

LinangData shall not be liable for any data uploaded by a user and any user that uploads Sensitive Information on LinangData.com

Securing your data
------------------

LinangData will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, unauthorized access, misuse, disclosure, alteration or destruction of your Personal Information.

LinangData supports SSL (HTTPS) communications whenever applicable, with the intent of further protecting your privacy and further providing security for your data.

Disclosing your Personal Information
------------------------------------

LinangData may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, LinangData may disclose your Personal Information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

If LinangData is being acquired or merges with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners in order to facilitate ongoing operations

Cross-border data transfers
---------------------------

Information that LinangData collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which LinangData operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. You agree to such cross-border transfers of Personal Information.

Updating this statement
-----------------------

LinangData may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. LinangData will notify you of any changes by posting a new version of the Privacy Statement on this website.

Other websites
--------------

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

2024 LinangData

[Privacy](https://linangdata.com/privacy.html) · [Terms](https://linangdata.com/terms.html) · [Contact](#contactModal)

##### Contact details

For more information contact: [info@linangdata.com](mailto:info@linangdata.com)
